What's up my kids How are you
Qué pasa mi chavalería Cómo estáis
I hope you're having a
Espero que estéis teniendo un día
spectacular day welcome one more day to my
espectacular bienvenidos un día más a mi
channel I'm Javier Oliveira if you don't
canal soy Javier oliveira si no me
know me subscribe right now or rather
conoces suscríbete ahora mismo o sea
but subscribe right now and you'll
pero suscríbete ahora mismo y ya vas a
understand why you're going to want to
entender el porqué vas a querer
subscribe you're going to want to like
suscribirte vas a querer darle like a
this video and share it without even having
este vídeo y compartirlo sin ni siquiera
seen it in full yet You already know
haberlo visto completo todavía Ya sabéis
that normally on this channel I only upload
que normalmente en este canal solo subir
each day in newscasts and I quickly
cada día en noticieros y te voy
inform you of all the news about
informando de toda la actualidad
your youtubers streamers and
rápidamente de tus youtubers streamers y
all the viral things that happen on the
de todas las cosas virales que pasa en
Internet but as I have you
Internet pero como ya os tengo
accustomed when something happens like what I
acostumbrados cuando pasa algo Como lo
bring today and when I bring an
que traigo hoy y cuando Traigo una
important exclusive I dedicate not
exclusiva importante le dedico no
only a video to it but I have to
solamente un vídeo sino que os tengo que
tell you that the exclusive that I bring today is not
decir que la exclusiva que traigo hoy no
going to leave anyone indifferent I don't sell
va a dejar indiferente a nadie no vendo
smoke you know that smoke is never sold here that
humo ya sabéis que aquí jamás se vende
when I have news to
humo que cuando tengo una noticia que
give you I give it but when I'm
daros la doy pero que cuando estoy
talking like this it's because I bring something big
hablando así es porque traigo algo gordo
very big here you have an appetizer of
muy gordo aquí tenéis una aperitivo de
what I'm going to tell you if I was
lo que os voy a comentar si estuve
talking with Ebay it was  commenting
hablando con Ebay estuvo comentando
on Coco and it seems that not
sobre Coco y Parece ser que la cosa no
only are things not going well but ibai would be
solamente no anda bien sino que ibai
considering coming out at some
estaría planteándose salir en algún
point to explain his version of
momento a explicar su versión de los
events and probably give the final blow
hechos y darle la última estocada
to the almost just a couple of
probablemente al casi apenas un par de
months ago was the protagonist at the Main of
meses fue el protagonista en el Main de
his most multitudinous event get
su evento más multitudinario poneros
comfortable and clench your asses because what I
cómodos y apretar el culo porque lo que
have to tell you in this video is not going
os tengo que comentar en este vídeo no
to leave anyone indifferent This
va a dejar indiferente a nadie Este
video is surely going to be the start of
vídeo seguramente va a ser el inicio de
something big and you can tell
algo gordo y podréis contar a todo el
everyone who saw it first here without
mundo que lo visteis primero aquí sin
further delay I am going to tell you what
más dilación me dispongo a contaros lo
happened give you a little
que ha pasado a daros un poco de
context and also draw some
contexto y también a sacar algunas
conclusions yesterday
conclusiones en el día de ayer se
an interview that coco did on
viralizó una entrevista que hizo coco en
a YouTube channel went viral in which he stated
un canal de YouTube en la que afirmaba
that he was currently no longer friends with ibai
que actualmente ya no era amigo de ibai
that iba and he had lost their friendship and
que iba y él habían perdido la amistad y
despite the fact that it is not the first time that he has
a pesar de que no es la primera vez que
mentioned it that iba and he are no longer
lo menciona que iba y él ya no son
friends, he wanted to lower the intensity and
amigos él quiso rebajar la intensidad y
attribute it to the fact that ibai is not
achacarlo como a que ibai no es
accessible and that he never messages and I
accesible y que no nunca los mensajes y
understand that for him it is super frustrating
entiendo que para él es súper frustrante
also to flirt with her on the rebound yes  He has
también ligarla de rebote si él no tiene
nothing to do with me, people
nada que ver conmigo la gente
literally told him he's the
literalmente le decía él es el amigo del
rapist's friend, I mean, it doesn't make sense.
violador o sea entender no tiene sentido
But anyway, the thing is that I think
Pero bueno la cuestión es que yo creo
putting up with all of that wore down
que bancarse todo eso desgastó mucho
our relationship a lot without meaning to and today, no,
nuestra relación sin querer y hoy no no
we are not friends, unfortunately, no, you don't
somos amigos lamentablemente no no te
talk to each other anymore, you no longer have a relationship, no, I
hablas más no tenés más relación no yo
try, but I think that nothing,
intento pero pero yo creo que que nada
regardless of the fact that everyone I
que independientemente que todo el mundo
ask tells me that he doesn't
al que le pregunto me dicen que tampoco
answer them either, what happens with Ibai is that his
les contesta lo que pasa con ibai Es que
agenda, the days, the hours,
la agenda los días los horarios
the level of work he has makes it
el nivel del laburo que tiene hace que
impossible to be active to make time to be
vivacidad imposible por ahí hacerse un
able to answer a
lugar para para poder contestar un
message. I also understand that he must have
mensaje también lo entiendo debe tener
messages from all over the world, up to this
mensajes de el mundo entero hasta este
point, what I can comment on based on my
punto lo que puedo comentar bajo mi
experience. The fact is that I am not friends
experiencia Es que yo que no soy amigo
with Ibai and I have spoken very few times with
de ibai y he hablado muy pocas veces con
him, barely 6 7 8 times, something like that, I
él apenas 6 7 8 veces algo así por el
think that on all occasions
estilo creo que en todas las ocasiones
except one, he has always started the
menos en una siempre ha iniciado en la
conversation, or he has asked me about
conversación o bien me ha preguntado por
a program or he has made a
algún programa o bien me ha hecho algún
joke about a live show of mine that he
chiste sobre algún directo mío que
was watching. I think the only time that
estaba viendo creo que la única vez que
he started the conversation with him was
el inicio la conversación yo a él fue
because of an event that was in Seville
por un evento que había en Sevilla al
that  I was going to go microphone in hand because you
que yo iba a ir micrófono en mano que ya
know that sometimes I go out on the
sabéis que algunas veces salgo a la
street and I asked him if he was coming I don't
calle y le pregunté que si él venía no
remember if it was to help me with
me acuerdo si era para que me facilitara
something or something like that I don't remember
algo o algo por el estilo no me acuerdo
but as I tell you I do not have a friendship
pero ya os digo yo no tengo una amistad
with him I think we have a cordial relationship I
con él Creo que tengo una cordialidad yo
take for granted that I have a cordial relationship
doy por hecho que tengo una cordialidad
because I do not have any problem with this
porque no tengo ningún problema con este
man only some differences and
hombre solamente algunas diferencias y
disagreements for obvious reasons and he
desacuerdos por motivos obvios y a mí
always answers my messages in
siempre me responde a los mensajes de
fact the conversation we had
hecho la conversación que hemos tenido
today and yesterday was quite fluid So
hoy y ayer fue bastante fluida Así que
I think we should completely rule out
yo creo que debemos descartar por
the theory that Goku has that he was going
completo la teoría es que tiene Goku de
and he is very busy so busy
que iba y está muy ocupado tan ocupado
that he can never answer the
de que no le puede contestar nunca los
messages to the one who was the protagonist the
mensajes al que fue el protagonista el
Main of his last most important event
Main de su último evento más importante
the event that has broken audiences and
del el evento que ha roto audiencias y
here what is happening is something else with
aquí lo que está pasando es otra cosa de
all this paraphernalia I would
toda esta parafernalia yo me quedaría
only stick with this phrase ibai and I
solamente con esta frase ibai y yo no
are not friends today it wore down a lot
somos amigos a día de hoy desgastó mucho
in our relationship without wanting to and today no we
en nuestra relación sin querer y hoy no
are not friends Unfortunately with VAT
no somos amigos Lamentablemente con IVA
and no you do not talk to each other anymore you no longer have a
y no no te hablas más no tenés más
relationship no I try but but I think that
relación no yo intento pero pero yo creo
nothing  that this is not the first time
que que nada que no es la primera vez
that Costco would claim this
que Costco afirmaría este
distancing, there have been several occasions,
distanciamiento ya hubo varias ocasiones
specifically I remember one day before
en concreto recuerdo una días antes de
the evening when Coscu was already
la velada en que coscu ya estaba dando a
implying that he was going and he was becoming
entender que iba y se le hacía
inaccessible, that when I wanted to have
inaccesible que cuando quería tener
some dealings with him or some conversation
algún Trato con él o alguna conversación
with him, he goes and didn't pay attention to him, and they
con él y va y no lo atendía a lo que me
ask me about Ibai, Ibai, I don't know what to
preguntan por ibai ibai no sé qué
tell you about Ibai, no, no, no, always when I don't
decirles de ibai no no no siempre que no
know him, there it goes, deep down I
lo conozco ahí va ahí en la profundidad
feel that Ibai is a great guy but that he
siento que ibai es un tipazo pero que
has so much work and that he has so much
tiene tanto trabajo y que tiene Tanto
stress that he can't bring out his true
estrés que no puede sacar su verdadera
personality, so it's like I don't
personalidad entonces como que no lo
know him,
conozco
saying that he's an incredible guy because I
diciendo que es un tipo increíble porque
knew him, I thought he was very good,
lo conocí de él me pareció muy bueno
but but he's very stressed, he's
pero pero está está muy estresado está
very stressed and I understand it, so I
muy estresado y lo entiendo entonces
always respect Ibai and the banks, are you
siempre respeto para ibai y los bancos
going to remind me in the
me vais a recordar ustedes en la caja de
comments box of what other occasions Coscu
comentarios en qué otras ocasiones coscu
gave to understand that he was going and did not respond to his
dio a entender que iba y no le respondía
messages, but it also comes
ya los mensajes pero también se me viene
to mind that when Coscu had that
a la cabeza que cuando coscu tuvo esa
attitude, the editor will be putting
actitud por aquí os estará poniendo el
some tweets here laughing at By
editor algunos tweets riéndose de By
virus because he knew he was injured. There it goes  and he also did
virus porque sabía lesionado Ahí va y
n't like one bit the day that
tampoco le gustó un pelo el día que
someone is announcing his injury it
alguien está anunciando su lesión a mí
seems strange to me honestly it
me parece raro sinceramente a mí me
seems strange to me the day that a player gets
parece raro el día que un jugador se
injured to leave him it seems
lesiona para irte de él a mí me parece
strange to me it seems like quite
raro me parece una conducta bastante
unsportsmanlike behavior it seems to me like
antideportiva a mí me parece una
quite unsportsmanlike behavior to laugh at
conducta bastante antideportiva reírte
someone who is injured doubting
de alguien que está lesionado dudar de
whether he is injured or not because he is
si está lesionado o no porque tiene
scared weird weird but oh well without further ado we already
miedo raro raro pero bueno sin más ya
know how these types
sabemos además Cómo funcionan este tipo
of events work in fact I can add another
de eventos de hecho puedo Añadir otra
thing and this is already a subjective opinion
cosa y esto ya es opinión subjetiva
completely subjective on my part in
completamente subjetiva por mi parte en
that click that goes viral in which Goku
ese clic que se viraliza en el que Goku
gets on his knees Thanking ibai for
se pone de rodilla Agradeciendo a ibai
not having taken him out of the event and
que no lo haya sacado del evento y le
apologizes for all the complications
pide perdón por todas las complicaciones
that have arisen by having him there I
que ha surgido por tenerlo ahí metido yo
notice a certain discomfort on
noto cierta incomodidad por parte de
ibai's part it is true that he responds and
ibai sí que es verdad que le responde y
half responds to the hug but
le medio responde al abrazo pero no
I do not feel the chemistry and the complicity
siento yo la química y la complicidad
that I would have in a few moments Like
que tendría yo en unos momentos Como
those with a friend of mine or with a person
esos con un amigo mío o con una persona
that at least I appreciate what did not go up
que como mínimo aprecio lo que no subió
after the fight
después del combate
Thank you for inviting me Sorry for all the
Gracias por invitarme Perdón por todos
problems we have had to exhaust
los problemas hemos tenido que agotar
too quickly
demasiado rápido
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
I have to warn you that after the
tengo que avisaros de que después de la
conversation I had with ibai both
conversación que tuve con ibai tanto
last night and in the last few hours, I think
anoche como en las últimas horas creo
that there are several things here that we don't know
que aquí hay varias cosas que no sabemos
and they don't look good at all
y no pintan bien absolutamente nada bien
for coscu but I don't know if they really
para coscu pero no sé si realmente
look good for ibai either. Actually,
pintan tampoco bien para ibai realmente
some of the things that he told me and
alguna de las cosas que me comentó y
what a night it was worried me a little. I have
vaya noche me preocuparon un poco yo he
spoken to him and I have made it very clear to him
hablado con él y le he dejado bien claro
that I am going to make this video, so let's
que voy a hacer este vídeo por lo tanto
see, this is not my way of working when
a ver no es mi forma de trabajar cuando
people tell me something privately it is
la gente me cuenta algo por privado es
private and that's it. No, if you knew all
privado y punto No si supierais todas
the things I know about youtubers and
las cosas que sé de los youtubers y de
streamers, I would keep quiet. Simply
los streamers que me callo Simplemente
because they have told me in a
porque me lo han contado en un ámbito de
confidential environment, but on this occasion, and he
confianza pero en esta ocasión y va y
knows that I have to make this video, I
sabe que tengo que hacer este vídeo que
have to inform you and I will do it in the
tengo que informaros y lo haré de la
most professional and objective way
manera más profesional y objetiva
possible, but I don't know how to interpret this,
posible pero no sé cómo interpretar esto
really, I am going to give you the data and I
realmente os voy a dar los datos y
want you to draw your
quiero que ustedes saquéis vuestras
own conclusions, although I can't
propias conclusiones aunque no puedo
deny that I would have liked him to
negar que me hubiese gustado que iba a
come here and tell me things more clearly.
ir aquí y me dijera las cosas más claras
had the opportunity last night to
ha tenido la oportunidad anoche da la
review he uploaded a video in which he
review subió un vídeo en el que se papeó
completely beat up ibai and honestly with
al ibai por completo y sinceramente con
all the reason in the world you dodge with
toda la razón del mundo esquiváis con
what he has done condemning rubiales he has
esto que ha hecho condenando a rubiales
had the nerve he has not had the
ha tenido la cara dura no ha tenido la
face of a diamond and it is that any
cara como el diamante y es que cualquier
beating from any saska that they gave him
papea de cualquier saska que le dieran
in the last few days Not only was it
en los últimos días No Solamente era
completely deserved but he
completamente merecida sino que es que
was also giving it away when I
además la estaba regalando cuando yo
was commenting last night on this
estaba anoche comentando Este vídeo de
Dallas video and I was
Dallas y además estuve comentando
also commenting on coscu's interview stating
también la entrevista de coscu afirmando
that ibai is no longer his friend he received a
que ibai ya no es su amigo recibió un
message in the middle of the live stream that left me
mensaje en pleno directo que me dejó con
completely broken and it was a
el culo completamente roto y era un
message from eBay Llanos one day I will tell
mensaje de eBay Llanos algún día contaré
the story of Goku I think the only one
la historia de Goku creo que el único
who knows is me and another person when I
que la sabe soy yo y otra persona cuando
cut the live stream I wanted to continue the
corté el directo quise seguir la
conversation with him because obviously you ca
conversación con él porque evidentemente
n't throw that at me Knowing what I
no me puedes lanzar eso Sabiendo a lo
do and Knowing what my
que me dedico y Sabiendo Cuál es mi
job is and what my vocation is and I have to
trabajo y cuál es mi vocación y tengo
pull the thread then here I
que tirar del hilo entonces aquí yo
can do two things I can offer you to
puedo hacer dos cosas puedo ofrecerte
give me all the information and
que me des toda la información y que me
clarify it directly or that I pull the
aclares directamente o que yo tire del
thread  to look for more information and
hilo que busque más información y que
draw my own conclusions the first thing
saque mis conclusiones lo primero que me
ibai told me and I noticed that I was
comentó ibai y yo Noté que estaba
pretty much on the verge of exploding was that I
bastante a punto de explotar era Pues
was a little fried from
que estaba un poco ya frito de estar
receiving blows for having silenced what you
recibiendo palos por haber silenciado lo
all know for having remained
que todos sabéis por haber mantenido
silent for seven months so I
silencio durante siete meses entonces yo
was proposing to him well go on
le estuve proponiendo bueno va
explain it to me explain to me what your version is
Explícamelo Explícame cuál es tu versión
explain to me what your point of view is and
Explícame cuál es tu punto de vista y
come tell it if you want I don't know if I
ven a contarlo si quieres no sé si
want to do it I feel that a lot of people would
quiero hacerlo siento que mucha gente
understand a lot of things but I don't know if it's
entendería muchas cosas pero no sé si es
a process that I feel like doing this
un proceso que me apetece hacer este
message The truth is that it generated
mensaje La verdad es que me generó
quite a few doubts for me Because honestly
bastante dudas Porque sinceramente se me
two options occurred to me that I was going with this he
ocurrieron dos opciones que iba con esto
was trying to explain to me that he
me estuviera intentando explicar que
has reasons or that he has a way of
tiene motivos o que tiene manera de
explaining why he had to remain
explicar por qué ha tenido que quedarse
silent and swallow coscu in the evening
callado y tragar con coscu en la velada
and that people would understand or on the other
y que la gente lo entendería o por otro
hand I was thinking of an option that I
lado estaba pensando una opción que
hope is not that one because if it is that one I'm
Espero que no sea esa porque si es esa
getting off this train that is to defend
yo me bajo de este tren que sea defender
and justify coscu sincerely I don't know
y justificar a coscu sinceramente no sé
how to interpret it but those are the two
cómo interpretarlo pero esas son las dos
options that he wants to justify that he
opciones que se quiera justificar que él
believes that he has a justification or an
crea que tiene una justificación o una
explanation for why  he has remained
explicación por la cual se ha quedado
silent for these seven months and has
callado durante estos siete meses y ha
swallowed coscu without saying it or that he
tragado con coscu sin sacarlo o que
really wants to justify
realmente quiera justificar la historia
coscu's story and see some explanation
de coscu y que le vea alguna explicación
because it has been told to him in another
porque se lo hayan contado de otra
way but I think that option is not I
manera pero creo que esa opción no es
think what happens here is that ibai
creo que aquí lo que pasa es que ibai se
has felt cornered he wanted to kick
ha visto acorralado ha querido echar a
Goku out of the evening and for some reason he was not
Goku de la velada y por algún motivo no
allowed this morning I have
le han permitido esta mañana me he
contacted him again I am not going
vuelto a poner en contacto con él no voy
to publish the conversation you know that
a publicar la conversación ya sabéis que
Although they tell you it is not my style to
Aunque os la cuenten no es mi estilo
bring up conversations I do not like that very much
sacar conversaciones no me gusta mucho
unless it is necessary but I think
eso a no ser que sea necesario pero creo
telling you is enough
que contaros lo es suficiente De todas
Anyway First I want to give a little
formas Primero quiero dar un poco de
context to how ibai's relationship
contexto a cómo surge la relación de
with coscu arose if I am wrong about something
ibai con coscu si me equivoco en algo
please correct me in the
por favor corregirme en la caja de
comments box and Bye and coscu meet for the
comentarios y Bye y coscu se conocen por
first time in person in July 2021
primera vez en persona en julio de 2021
in July 2021 ibai invites Coco to
en julio de 2021 ibai invita a Coco a
visit his house and they do several
que visite su casa y hacen varias
collaborations together Or a lot a lot of
colaboraciones juntos O mucho mucho
support from the coscu Army
apoyo de la coscu Army
we are representing Argentina
estamos representando Argentina
Latin America
latinoamérica
from Argentina that almost everyone
de Argentina que casi todos le
you will meet and it's the first time we've
conoceréis y es la primera vez que nos
seen each other in person today Well this morning And
vemos en persona hoy Bueno esta mañana Y
then Well the truth is that it's a
entonces Bueno pues la verdad que es un
special day no yes very special at
día especial no sí muy especial por lo
least for me and you're going to stay here
menos para mí y te vas a quedar aquí
well hopefully a month no maybe
pues esperemos que un mes no por ahí sí
but I don't want to bother me I imagine
pero no quiero molestar yo me imagino
that this type of collaboration would arise
que este tipo de colaboración surgiría
because he was and is a person of great
porque iba y es una persona de Gran
reach in Spain and of great reach on
alcance en España y de Gran alcance en
Twitch and on the other hand It seems that
Twitch y por otro lado Parece ser que
Goku for a while has had a
Goku durante un tiempo ha tenido como un
great reach in his country like he has been
gran alcance en su país como que ha sido
one of the main streamers in
uno de los principales streamers de
fact one of those who had the most power on
hecho de los que más poder tenían en
Twitch And well they are simply
Twitch Y pues son simplemente
business collaborations that are
colaboraciones empresariales que se
made Well for work there's nothing
hacen Pues por curro no tiene nada de
wrong with it depends on who I choose of course
malo depende A quién elija por supuesto
but these are very common things among
pero son cosas muy habituales entre las
people who are dedicated to what we are
personas que nos dedicamos a los que nos
dedicated to It turns out that ibai and coscu
dedicamos Resulta ser que ibai y coscu
also coincide in some tastes in
coinciden también en algunos gustos en
some tastes and in some interests
algunos gustos y en algunos intereses
Like for example especially football
Como por ejemplo especialmente el fútbol
on that flight from Argentina to Spain also does
en ese vuelo desde Argentina a España
not coincide with Kun Agero
tampoco coincide con el Kun Agüero al
Kun Agero would be used to
Kun Agüero estaría acostumbrados ahora a
seeing him around here on Twitch streaming
verlo por aquí por Twitch stremeando
but at that time although not
pero en aquella época aunque no hace
long ago if not  I'm wrong, he was still
mucho tiempo si no me equivoco todavía
playing, as I was saying, on that flight,
jugaba como iba diciendo en ese vuelo el
Kun Agero met Goku and they had,
Kun Agüero coincide con Goku y tienen
like, their first contact, and now he's in a bit of a relationship
como la primera toma de contacto y ahora
with Kun. Yes, we talked a
está algo con el Kun Sí hablamos un
lot, we talked about a band, for example, he
montón hablamos una banda por ejemplo me
surprised me with things for my son. I
sorprendió con cosas para mi hijo Yo
thought so too, and for example, he was
pensé que también y por ejemplo era
super funny and made a lot of jokes,
súper divertido y Hacía un montón de
and he also told me, he says he laughs
chistes y él me dijo también dice ríe
a lot at the jokes, but he's not the one who makes them. Who is Papu? No, I thought so too, but Papu laughs too. [Music] He invites the Spanish, from what I've been checking during the month that Coscu has been in Spain, they have had several contacts with Kun Agero, and it
varios contactos con el Kun Agüero y se
turns out that Kun surprises them by
tercia que el Kun les da la sorpresa de
visiting and meeting Messi, it's a
visitar y conocer a Messi es una
very important experience in
experiencia muy importante en la vida de
both of their lives, which, as they say, they share
ambos que como quien dice comparten
together. Holding hands, I
juntos de la mano
was on my phone, 34 paparazzi, and I say,
estaba con el móvil 34 paparachis y digo
what the hell is going on here,
pero esto qué [__] está pasando aquí
but paparazzi, not from
pero paparachis no de no de cámara de
Tere's camera, but from a paparazzi. Well, I don't know what
Tere sino de paparachi Bueno no sé qué
camera it is, the one I zoom in on,
cámara es de esta que le meto el zoom a
damn Pantoja, and a lot of
la Pantoja [__] y pero un montón de
guys iba ibai I say of course I
chavales iba ibai digo claro estoy
understand everything Kun has brought us to
entendiendo todo el Kun nos ha traído a
his house the press knows the people
su casa la prensa lo sabe el pueblo lo
know and they have come to ask him to
sabe y han venido a preguntarle que a
see what the hell he thinks about Messi
ver qué [__] piensa de lo de Messi
I saw him a little uncomfortable because you see there
Yo le vi un poco incómodo porque ya ves
are journalists the kids hitting
haya periodistas los niños dando hostias
the window and I saying But what is
en el cristal y yo diciendo Pero qué
going on this video that I appear
está pasando este vídeo que yo aparezco
as if I were calmly in the
como que estoy tranquilamente en el
car since I am like another day
coche que ya que estoy como un día más
I am there with the I am there with my arm
estoy ahí con la estoy ahí con el brazo
out as if I were your father who is
puesto como si fuese tu padre que está
sunbathing with his arm and saying
tomando el sol con el brazo y diciendo
what's up to everyone it's that I didn't know where I
qué tal a todos es que yo no sabía dónde
was I want a surprise from this guy and and
iba Quiero una sorpresa de este tío y y
people this guy is like another
la gente este tío va como un día más
clear day because for me I was going to
claro porque yo para mí Estaba yendo a
a restaurant to have dinner that's why I was like that
un restaurante a cenar por eso iba así
because I don't know what the [ __ ] I'm going to know is
porque yo no sé yo qué [__] voy a saber
Messi's house if I see a
que la casa de Messi si veo una puerta
garage door let me tell you the story a
de un garaje a mí déjame de historia un
work colleague with whom you have
compañero de trabajo con el que tienes
these types of experiences no matter how much you have
este tipo de experiencias por mucho que
known him for a short time if I
lo conozcas de hace poco tiempo si te
send you some messages or he is trying to
mando unos mensajes o está intentando
chat with you you answer him it is more
charlar contigo tú le contesta es más
than evident that today ibai and
que evidente que a día de hoy ibai y
coscu have a  bad vibes and according to what I'm
coscu tienen un mal rollo y según Me
told at some point ibai is going to come
comentan en algún momento ibai va a
out and tell his version before
salir a contar su versión antes de
I tell you the following I will tell you a
comentaros lo siguiente os comento un
little about the conversation I had with
poco la conversación que he tenido con
ibai this morning I was
ibai esta mañana yo le he estado
telling him that obviously I had
comentando que evidentemente tenía que
to pull on this thread and that I was not going to remain as if nothing had happened after what he told me last night that of course before investigating on my own I preferred that he tell me the story before speculating or being wrong for example You know that on other
por ejemplo Ya sabéis que en otras
occasions there have been big stories
ocasiones ha habido movidas muy grandes
about other youtubers and they come to me they
de otros youtubers y ellos vienen me
tell me things they clarify them for me and
cuentan cosas me las aclaran y yo en
based on that I can inform more
base a eso o puedo informar más en
properly than with speculation and
condiciones que con especulaciones y
such well ibai has told me that he
demás bien pues ibai me ha comentado que
prefers to tell the whole story
prefiere contar toda la historia que
behind the evening when he
hubo detrás de la velada cuando se
feels ready when the
sienta preparado cuando llegue el
moment comes he knows perfectly well the
momento sabe perfectamente la
repercussions that this subject is going to have he
repercusión que va a tener este tema él
thinks and is convinced that when
piensa y está convencido de que cuando
he tells his point of view the majority
él cuente su punto de vista la mayoría
of people are going to understand it he has been
de las personas lo van a entender lleva
thinking about doing this for a long time that is
mucho tiempo pensando en hacer esto por
why For example I think that yesterday when he
eso Por ejemplo yo creo que ayer cuando
was watching our live he got heated
estaba viendo nuestro directo se calentó
suddenly and he sent me those messages but there's
de repente y me mandó esos mensajes pero
something that puts him off and I don't
hay algo que lo Echa para atrás y no
quite understand what it is the
termino de entender qué es lo que es lo
only thing he's confirmed to me is that at
único que me ha confirmado es que en
some point he'll do it that he wants to do
algún momento lo hará que quiere hacer
it calmly in a chat of a
lo tranquilamente en una charla de un
couple of hours in the appropriate place he
par de horas en el sitio adecuado me ha
told me I don't know what he means by that
dicho no sé a qué se refiere con eso
but I understand that there he rules me out or
pero yo entiendo que ahí me descarta o
rules out any other channel I think
descarta cualquier otro canal Yo creo
the appropriate place is with Piqu now I
que el sitio adecuado es con Piqué ahora
'll explain why and that he wants to
os explicaré el porqué y que quiere
comment in detail the whole process
comentar con detalles todo el proceso
of the event
del evento
I warned you before the video I
os He avisado antes del vídeo os He
warned you in advance that
avisado con tiempo de que la información
today's information wasn't just any I warned you
de hoy no era cualquiera os He avisado
that smoke is never sold here
que aquí no se vende humo nunca hace
approximately two years ago with this thing that he
aproximadamente dos años con esto de que
went and knows some Agero from there he knows
iba y conoce algún Agüero de ahí conoce
Messi from there he starts to meet
a Messi de ahí se empieza a conocer con
several footballers you know that a
varios futbolistas ya sabéis que hace un
couple of years ago ibai not only had the
par de años ibai no solamente tenía los
rights to some leagues to
derechos de algunas ligas para
broadcast and comment on them but he also
retransmitirlas y comentarlas sino que
started to rub shoulders more than necessary with
empezó a codearse más de la cuenta con
a lot of footballers this has been by
un montón de futbolistas esto ha sido de
mutual agreement Because some footballers
mutuo acuerdo Porque algunos futbolistas
when they are finishing their career this
cuando van Terminando su carrera esto
also happens with the  TV I have
pasa también con lo de la tele Yo tengo
another channel called Telesalseo where
otro canal que se llama telesalseo donde
I move in the atmosphere of
pues me muevo con el ambiente de los
gossip journalists some
periodistas del corazón vienen algunos
famous people come to be interviewed and this
famosos a ser entrevistados y esto pues
is an exchange of interests although soccer
es un intercambio de intereses aunque
players during their
los futbolistas durante sus épocas
golden age are millionaires and earn a lot of
doradas sean millonarios y ganen mucha
money when they can no longer practice their
pasta cuando ya no pueden ejercer su
profession they are still very young they have their
profesión son todavía muy jóvenes tienen
whole lives ahead of them and they usually make
toda la vida por delante y suelen hacer
investments and put their eggs in several
inversiones y poner los huevos en varias
baskets Well there are several soccer players and I think you
canastas Pues hay varios futbolistas y
will have noticed these and there
creo que de estos habréis dado cuenta y
is no secret that they have made an
no hay ningún secreto que han hecho un
approach to the streamers who have
acercamiento a los streamers que han
seen a bit of their Target and with more
visto un poco de su Target y con más
influence to join them or I
influencia para juntarse con ellos o
could say a long list of
podría decir una larga lista de
soccer players who are collaborating
futbolistas que están colaborando a día
today with the most viewed streamers in
de hoy con los streamers más vistos de
our country and in Latin America And this
nuestro país y de latinoamérica Y esto
is an exchange of interests There it goes and
es un intercambio de intereses Ahí va y
for example he loves being surrounded by
por ejemplo le flipa está rodeado de
soccer players and the soccer players take
futbolistas y los futbolistas se
advantage of the publicity ibai has
aprovechan de la publicidad ibai los ha
put ibai in the spotlight Hey maybe
puesto ibai en el candelero Oye que a lo
they would have opened channels and they would
mejor ellos hubieran abierto canales y
also have had repercussions it
también hubieran tenido repercusión
could be this move we also have
puede ser esta movida también la tenemos
in the topics of the heart  Those of you who
nosotros en los temas del corazón los
follow me on telesalseo know that this
que me sigáis en telesalseo sabéis que
also happens and this is a Fifty this is
también pasa y esto es un Fifty esto es
an agreement okay the move is that Piqu
un acuerdo vale la movida es que Piqué
is the owner of Cosmos and what is Cosmos you will
es el dueño de Cosmos y que es Cosmos os
ask yourself Piqu has seen a
preguntaréis Piqué ha visto una
golden opportunity to increase his
oportunidad de oro para incrementar su
fortune with the purchase and exploitation of
fortuna con la compra y explotación de
the television rights of football the
los derechos televisivos del fútbol el
first step has been to acquire the
primer paso ha sido hacerse con los
rights to the Copa Amrica in Spain
derechos de la Copa América en España
a very attractive competition for
una competición muy atractiva para Los
fans of this sport but given the
amantes de este deporte pero que dada la
time difference with Spain and the
diferencia horaria con España y la
coincidence in calendars with the
coincidencia en calendarios con la
Eurocup meant that no major
Eurocopa hizo que ningún gran medio
Spanish media was interested in acquiring
español le interesara por hacerse con
them Gerard and Cosmos got it
ellos Gerard y Cosmos lo consiguieron
after acquiring them he chose one of
tras hacerse con ellos escogió a uno de
the best communicators at a
los mejores comunicadores a nivel
national level such as ibai Llanos the
nacional como es ibai Llanos el streamer
Spanish streamer cast the most
español casteó los partidos más
interesting matches of the competition with the
interesantes de la competición con la
luck of experiencing an Argentina Brazil in
suerte de vivir una Argentina Brasil en
the final the first international title
la final el primer título internacional
for Leo Messi they achieved large
de Leo Messi consiguieron grandes
audiences on ibai's Twitch Channel
audiencias en el Canal de Twitch de ibai
something that they used to promote at the
algo que utilizaron para promocionar al
same time the next edition of the
mismo tiempo la próxima edición de la
Davis Cup after this they have tried to acquire
Copa Davis tras esto han intentado
the rights to the series an
hacerse con los derechos de la serie una
attractive competition that has  with
competición atractiva que cuenta con
great teams and players however it has been
grandes equipos y jugadores sin embargo
an impossible task for them since they were
les ha resultado una tarea imposible Ya
facing giants like ESPN
que se enfrentaban a gigantes como ESPN
or Mediapro Gerald Piqu is the founder,
o mediapro gerald Piqué es el fundador
the seo, the president and I don't know how many
el seo el presidente y no sé cuántas
other things in the Cosmo society What is the
cosas más en la sociedad Cosmo Qué es la
Cosmo society, the Cosmo society right now
sociedad Cosmo la sociedad Cosmo ahora
if I'm not mistaken Manages and has
mismo si no me equivoco Maneja y tiene
The spider's web other societies that involve
La telaraña otra sociedades que implican
the management of koi and the management of the
el manejo de koi y el manejo de la
evening of the year among many other
velada del año entre otras muchas cosas
important things Cosmos you can look it up
importantes Cosmos podéis buscarlo por
there the data is public and this is what there
ahí los datos son públicos y esto es lo
is with this it comes to mind
que hay con esto se me viene a la cabeza
and I remember again one of the last
y vuelvo a recordar uno de los últimos
messages that
mensajes que me manda ibai esta mañana
ibai sent me this morning I will do it Chatting calmly in a place where I can be calm talking for a couple of hours and explain everything in the right place the right place and where he was and is going to feel comfortable to try and tell his version of what happened during the evening or after the
de lo ocurrido en la velada o tras la
evening Surely he is referring to being on
velada Seguramente se refiere a serlo en
a set with Gerard Piqu and I do
un plató junto a Gerard Piqué y es que
n't know if you agree
no sé si ustedes estáis de acuerdo
with me but I have come to the
conmigo pero yo he llegado a la
conclusion and I just realized  today
conclusión y me acabo de dar cuenta hoy
if cocu had to be expelled
que de haber tenido que expulsar a cocu
from the evening Gerard Piqu would also have a
de la velada Gerard Piqué también
say in fact I just
tendría voz y voto de hecho me acabo de
realized that maybe it would be more
dar cuenta que tal vez sería más
Gerard's decision than ibai's own let's
decisión de Gerard que del propio ibai a
see I understand that if eBay puts
ver que entiendo que si eBay se le meten
the balls to kick someone out they have to kick them out
los [__] echar a alguien lo tienen
in the end it's their event and it's their
que echar al final es su evento y es su
channel and if they insist I imagine they will
canal y si se empeña yo me imagino que
succeed but we can't ignore that
lo consigue pero no podemos obviar que
the company is what it is and that Gerard
la sociedad es la que es y que Gerard
has to approve it therefore here I can think of
tiene que aprobarlo por lo tanto aquí se
several things that prevent
me ocurren varias cosas que impiden a
eBay to this day although it is
eBay hasta el día de hoy aunque está
eager to do so and will do so at any
deseando hacerlo y lo hará en cualquier
moment from speaking clearly and giving its version of
momento hablar claro y dar su versión de
why it couldn't remove coscu from the
Por qué no pudo sacar a coscu de la
evening option number one that I put on
velada opción número uno que pongo sobre
the table cojo confirmed at a certain point
la mesa cojo confirmó en cierto momento
before the evening that he and I were going to have
antes de la velada que iba y él llegaron
a meeting with his lawyers in which
a tener una reunión con sus abogados en
his lawyer would warn ibai
las que su abogado le advertiría a ibai
that if he decides to remove him from the evening there
que si se le ocurre sacarlo de la velada
would be legal consequences and the
tendría consecuencias legales y lo
important thing is that ibai when he
importante del punto es que ibai cuando
had the meeting with me because of what
tuvo la reunión conmigo por lo que
was happening and with my lawyers and everything  He
estaba pasando y con mis abogados y todo
understood what the reality was what
entendió Cuál era la realidad Cuál era
the truth was and that he couldn't get me out of the
la verdad y que no podía sacarme de la
evening because if he had taken me out of the evening he would have been an
velada Porque si me sacaba la velada
accomplice to that
estaba haciendo cómplice de esa
accusation this is important I never
acusación esto es importante yo nunca lo
said it I think he didn't take me out because my
dije yo creo que él no me sacó porque mi
friend but you also have to understand that
amigo pero también hay que entender que
he doesn't want to be an accomplice to the
él no quiere ser cómplice de la
accusation because my lawyer obviously
acusación porque mi abogado Obviamente
gave him to understand that if like the
le dio a entender que si como las
evidence Dallas was breaking the balls
pruebas Dallas a romper las pelotas
and well obviously we had the
estaba y bueno obviamente teníamos las
evidence that everything that was being
pruebas que todo lo que se está se me
accused of me was false and there
estaba acusando era falso y ahí
obviously they decided to keep us at the
obviamente decidieron mantenernos en la
evening because if they didn't keep us
velada porque si no nos mantenían
obviously in some way they were
obviamente de alguna manera estaban
implying that they were joining the
dando a entender que que se sumaban a la
wave of a rapist it is understandable because I am who I am I
ola de un violador se entiende porque yo
know the things that I did and I know
soy quien soy sé las cosas que hice y sé
how far I am from being
lo lejos que estoy de ser una Escoria
human scum like the one they say I am so
humana como la que dicen que soy así que
enjoy me because I will be at the evening
disfrútenme porque yo en la velada voy a
and thank you for having believed in me
estar y agradezca por haber creído en mí
and in the evidence in everything that I
y en las pruebas en todo lo que les
am telling you in that click that I just
estoy diciendo en ese clic que os acabo
put without cutting a hair Goku has just
de poner sin cortarse un pelo Goku acaba
affirmed that he threw his lawyers at
de afirmar que le echó sus abogados a
ibai and they warned him this doesn't
ibai y le advirtieron esto no tiene
look at all
pinta ni mucho menos de ser nada
friendly that if he removed him from the evening there
amistoso que si lo sacaba De la velada
would be legal consequences let's see I do
tendría consecuencias legales a ver yo
n't know if this was really going to happen and would put him
no sé si esto realmente iba y le echaría
off and if this is really the
para atrás y si es este realmente el
reason why he didn't remove him from the
motivo por el que no lo sacó de la
evening if I were ibai and I hear this
velada yo si fuera ibai y escucho a este
guy saying this in a String about me
tío diciendo esto en un String sobre mí
I'll go out and clarify the thing that if it's
yo salgo y Lo aclaro la movida que si es
by contract because they have a clause
por contrato porque tengan una cláusula
in which they can no longer remove him as far
en la que ya no le puedan sacar yo hasta
as I understand and from what I've
donde tengo entendido Y por lo que he
seen on television programs If
visto en programas de televisión Si de
suddenly something as strong as what
repente sale algo tan fuerte como lo que
came out with Goku comes out you can have the
salió de Goku ya puedes tener la
clause you want because there is usually
cláusula que quieras que suele haber
another clause in which when there is something
otra cláusula en la que cuando hay algo
so reprehensible that it could
tan reprochable que puede perjudicar
even harm the event to the point that I think they have
Incluso el evento a tal punto que creo
lost sponsors you can go ahead
que han perdido sponsors tú puedes [__]
and remove him from the evening it would only be
y sacarlo de la velada solamente
missing or rather put yourself in the place and
faltaría o sea poneros en el lugar y
put yourself in the situation it would only be missing
poneros en la situación solo faltaba
come on and even if you had to
vamos y aunque incluso tuvieras que
pay a penalty you [ __ ]
pagar una penalización cagas billetes de
500 bills what does it matter what you pay with the evening they have
500 qué más da lo paga con la velada se
made millions of
han sacado de beneficios millones de
euros in profits millions and  I know the calculations
euros millones y se los cálculos
millions would have obviously
millones nos habría evidentemente
told us how much but millions but
deciros cuánto pero millones pero de
anyway no Anyway there is no
todas maneras que no De todas maneras
legal reproach for
que no hay ningún reproche legal para
ibai he does not have to take it out and
ibai él no tiene por qué sacarlo y
call him V or call him abu he could
llamarlo V ni llamarlo abu él podría
perfectly well take it out of the evening and
perfectamente sacarlo de la velada y
simply say that they have come out
decir simplemente que han salido
behavior of Goku that he reproaches
comportamiento de Goku que él reprocha
that does not go with the editorial line of the
que no va con la línea editorial de la
company and that they are acts that are
empresa y que son acti que están
completely against with the
completamente en contra con la
organization of the event simply with
organización del evento simplemente con
that he would not even be accusing him of anything and he
eso ni le estaría acusando De nada y
could perfectly well take it out but the
podría sacarlo perfectamente pero es que
thing is that it is not that you can take out
aparte es que no es que tú puedes sacar
whoever you want or rather if you are going to
a quien tú quieras o sea que si vais a
chanto with that he is very badly advised
chanto con eso está muy mal asesorado
to be such a millionaire he is very badly
para ser tan millonario está muy mal
advised and it is that only with the
asesorado y es que solamente con la
photograph that went viral and with the
fotografía que se hizo viral y con el
hidden live I think that there is enough
directo oculto yo creo que hay bastante
reason there to take a reproach
motivo ahí como para tomar un reproche
then on the other hand there is the second
luego por otro lado está la segunda
option the second option that occurs to me
opción la segunda opción que a mí se me
is that ibai did not do it for
ocurre es que ibai no lo hiciera por
fear that coscu had something about him that
miedo a que coscu tuviese algo de él que
the noble giant was not so noble and
el gigante noble no fuera tan noble y
that somehow he had him
que de alguna manera lo tuviera cogido
by the balls and that if he goes  and I would have taken him out
por los huevos y que si va y lo hubiera
of the evening Coscu would be spouting the
sacado de la velada coscu largaba la
traviata about Ibai but I don't know
traviata sobre ibai pero no lo sé la
honestly that's the other option I put on
verdad es la otra opción que pongo sobre
the table and then there would be the option that
la mesa y luego estaría la opción de que
Ibai is trying to tell me
lo que me está intentando decir ibai
would be that he knows the story well and that he
sería que él conoce bien la historia y
wants to defend Coco that really
que quiere defender a Coco que realmente
Kokku didn't do anything wrong or something like that
kokku no hizo nada malo o algo por el
but I think that's not the way it goes
estilo pero creo que por ahí no van los
at least I don't interpret it
tiros yo por lo menos no lo interpreto
that way besides By the way he was also
así además Por cierto también estuvo
saying that he had planned to do it
diciendo que tenía planeado hacerlo
After the evening once
Después de la velada una vez que
the evening was over, go out and prepare a
terminase la velada salir preparar un
program in the place that he has to
programa en el lugar que lo tiene que
do a two hour talk and tell
hacer una charla de dos horas y contarlo
everything tell everything that happened behind the scenes
todo contar todo lo que pasó por detrás
but that in the end for whatever reason he
pero que al final por el motivo que sea
backed out also whatever
se echó para atrás también lo que sea
happened I think he has some
que haya pasado Yo creo que tiene algún
kind of fear on the one hand he believes that by
tipo de temor por un lado él cree que
giving explanations of what happened and
dando explicaciones de lo que pasó y por
why he had to swallow that there will be people
qué tuvo que tragar que va a haber gente
who will understand it I still think
que lo va a entender Yo sigo pensando
that whatever it is it is coming late because I have done it
que sea lo que sea viene tarde porque lo
is done and at the event there was
he hecho hecho está Y en el evento ha
who should not have been there but
estado quien no tenía que estar pero
we will be waiting for that explanation and it
estaremos pendiente de esa explicación y
gives me  the feeling that maybe Piqu could have
me da la sensación que tal vez Piqué
also had something to do with it
también haya podido tener algo que ver
but I'm telling you this is what I have and he
pero ya os digo esto es lo que tengo y
goes and has thoughts of breaking the
va y tiene pensamientos de romper el
silence at any moment when
silencio en cualquier momento cuando
we least expect it and he wants to tell
menos nos lo Esperemos y quiere contar
how things happened the
cómo sucedieron las cosas la historia
full story behind the evening 3 why they
completa detrás de la velada 3 por qué
got to where they got to and in which
llegaron a donde llegaron y en la que
Gerard Piqu probably
probablemente Gerard Piqué haya tenido
also had his decision point we don't
también su punto de decisión no lo
know when that moment comes you
sabemos cuando llegue ese momento os
found out First here on Javier
enterasteis Primero aquí en Javier
Oliveira family I hope you
oliveira familia Espero que os haya
liked the video I hope it was to
gustado el vídeo espero que haya sido de
your liking If you have reached this
vuestro agrado Si habéis llegado a este
point I understand that yes for the moment
punto entiendo que sí por el momento
tomorrow we return to the normal and
mañana volvemos al contenido normal y
current content of the news do not forget to
corriente de noticiero no olvidéis
subscribe like share the
suscribiros darle like compartir el
video I send you a big hug
vídeo os mando un abrazo muy grande
follow me on Twitter follow me on
seguirme en Twitter seguirme en
Instagram tell me what you think about what we
instagram decidme qué os parece lo que
have talked about see you in the next
hemos hablado nos vemos en el siguiente
video bye
vídeo chao
[Music]
[Música]